

CONTACT

089-486-5651 p.tiansmith@gmail.com 1 Soi Pracha Chuen 32, Pracha Chuen Road, Wong Sawang, Bang Sue, Bangkok, Thailand 10800

SPECIALIZE IN

- LEADERSHIP & STRATEGIC MANAGEMENT
- PEOPLE DEVELOPMENT & TALENT MANAGEMENT
- DESIGN THINKING FOR BUSINESS INNOVATION
- BUSINESS TO GOVERNMENT (B2G)
- FRANCHISE MANAGEMENT

CERTIFICATES

- THE LEADER MANAGER BY WILSON LEARNING
- PERFORMANCE MANAGEMENT BY SIAM
 WILSON LEARNING

EDUCATION

DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY
PROGRAM IN HIGHER
EDUCATION

CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY 2009- 2015

MASTER OF SCIENCE PROGRAM IN RECREATION

KASETSART UNIVERSITY 2004 - 2006

BACHELOR OF ARTS PROGRAM IN PHYSICAL EDUCATION

KASETSART UNIVERSITY 2000 - 2004

PATARA TIANSMITH

GENERAL MANAGEMENT
ORGANIZATION & PEOPEL DEVELOPMENT

PROFILE

I worked about corporate management since 2016, focusing on develops organization strategies by identifying and researching human resources issues for design strategy and set goals for growth, control budgets and ensure more than 100 employees are motivated and productive.

During COVID-19 pandemic, I had an opportunity to initiate my own Edtech startup and eSports startup. My assets are how to create and manage a lean startup for business innovation.

LECTURER/FACILITATOR

- SCHOOL OF HRD, NIDA
 STRATEGIC LEARNING & COMPETITIVE ADVANTAGE
- FACULTY OF MBA, PANYAPIWAT INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT DESIGN THINKING FOR BUSINESS INNOVATION

WORK EXPERIENCE

O CO-FOUNDER & COO | 2022

EKA ESPORTS

- Raises funds from investors
- Setup company
- Talent Management

FOUNDER & CEO | 2019 - 2022

EDTECH STARTUP

- Managed budgets and find ways to increase revenue and profits
- Created an Online Learning Platform (WEB2)
- Managed outsourced software and blockchain developers
- Raises funds from Startup Accelerators

GENERAL MANAGER | 2016-2018

KPN ACADEMY

- Oversees company operations as Sales & Marketing, IT, HR, Budgeting
- Managed full-time employees of more than 100 people from both own branches and franchises, totaling 100 branches
- B2B and B2G Management

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER | 2010-2015

KPN MUSIC

- Plan and supervise for Business Format Franchise
- Expanded 50 music academies (franchise)
- Initiated music e-learning for school in Thailand and CLMV
- M&A education business and became KPN Academy

S P O R T S D I R E C T O R | 2007 - 2010 BANGKOK SUVARNABHUMI UNIVERSITY

- Oversight all things related to student affair & sports department.
- Supervised, hired, scheduled, trained and evaluated Assistant Sports Director, Sports Administration Specialist, coaches, officials, interns, volunteers and other part time employees